强森医生 七线有您电话
Dr. Johnson, you have a call on line 7.
她还没到… 我孩子的妈妈还没到
She's not here yet. She's having my baby and she's not here.
- 我相信没事的 羊水破了吗？ - 我不知道
- Everything's fine. Has her water broken?     - I don't know.
我们说话的时候 她说黏液栓子已经脱落了
But when I spoke to her, she said she'd already passed the mucus plug.
我们一定要知道这个吗？
Do we have to know about that?
乔伊 如果你小孩要生了怎么办？
What are you gonna do when you have a baby?
我会在候诊室分送雪茄
I'm gonna be in the waiting room, handing out cigars.
我猜乔伊安排了在50年代的电影生小孩
Yes, Joey's made arrangements to have his baby in a movie from the '50s.
我不敢相信 她有可能生在计程车上
Aah, I don't believe this. I mean, she could be giving birth in the cab.
罗斯 别紧张
Oh, Ross, relax.
第一次阵痛可能只要2块钱
It's only like $2 for the first contraction...
然后每次阵痛跳表5毛钱
...and then 50 cents each additional contraction.
怎样 钱德开玩笑就无所谓？
What, it's okay when Chandler does it?
你要会选时间
You have to pick your moments.
- 我错过了吗？ - 她还没到
- Hi. Did I miss it? Did I miss it?     - No, she's not even here yet.
- 哦   - 你背吉他干嘛？
- Oh.     - What's with the guitar?
我们可能要在这待一会儿 或许用得上音乐
I just thought we might be here for a while, so, you know, things might get musical.
- 你们去哪里了？ - 我们去了礼品店
- Hey, where the hell have you been?     - We stopped at the gift shop.
我买了玩偶 苏珊买了强奇巧克力棒
I was looking at stuffed animals, and Susan wanted a Chunky.
你要生小孩了 买什么强奇巧克力？
Susan wanted a... You're having a baby. A baby. You don't stop for Chunkys.
- 我以前有那种保险秆贴纸   - 哈
- I used to have that bumper sticker.     - Ha, ha.
你们懂我的意思吧？
You see what I mean?
- 还买巧克力   - 算了吧 罗斯
- "Stopped for a Chunky."     - Let it go, Ross.
我有多的 你要吗？
I got an extra one. You want this?
不要
No.
嘿 我最喜欢的父母档如何？
Hey, how's my favorite parenting team doing?
法兰兹布劳医生
Dr. Franzblau. Hi.
我知道你们想生小孩
So I understand you're thinking of having a baby.
哇
Wow.
你怀孕了9个月 那是很好的开始
I see you're nine months pregnant. That's a good start.
- 你的阵痛如何？ - 我很喜欢
- How you doing with your contractions?     - Oh, I love them.
每次都像有人在我的子宫狂欢
Each one's like a little party in my uterus.
间隔4分钟 持续55秒
Ha, ha. They're every four minutes and last 55 seconds.
是59秒 石英表
Fifty-nine seconds. Quartz. Ha.
端士石英表
Swiss quartz. Ha, ha.
- 我能喝东西吗？ - 可以吃冰块
- Am I allowed to drink anything?     - Ice chips, just ice chips.
- 护士站有   - 我去拿
- They're at the nurses' station.     - I'll get them.
- 不 我去拿   - 不 我要去了
- No, I'm getting it. Be right back.     - No, I got it. I'm getting it.
嗨 我在想你可能想要冰块
Hi. Thought you might like some ice chips.
谢谢
Thanks.
如果有任何需要 我…
And if you need anything else, I...
我想我们没有见过 你好
...do not believe we have met. Hi.
我是瑞秋•葛林
I'm Rachel Green.
我是卡萝前夫妹妹的室友
I'm Carol's ex-husband's sister's roommate. Ha, ha.
幸会 我是法兰兹布劳医生
It's nice to meet you. I'm Dr. Franzblau.
我是你室友哥哥前妻的产科医师
I'm your roommate's brother's ex-wife's obstetrician.
喔 好好笑
Oh, that's funny.
我想要个小孩
I want a baby.
今晚不行 宝贝 明天我要早起
Hmm. Not tonight, honey. I got an early day tomorrow.
起来 我们去倒杯咖啡
Get up. Come on, let's get some coffee.
好吧 因为我们从没这么做过
Oh, okay, because we never do that.
投篮…
Shoot, shoot, shoot.
或者不投 那也可以
Or just fall down. That's good too.
- 尼克队粉丝？ - 对
- Knick fan?     - Oh, yeah.
- 喔 天啊 他们真烂   - 听着 小姐…
- Oh, boy, do they suck.     - Hey, listen, lady, I...
哇哦
Whoa.
你看 看看你的尤恩 投得好
Look. Look at your man Ewing. Nice shot.
要是在船上 他连水都碰不到
You know, he couldn't hit water if he was standing on a boat.
是吗？那你喜欢谁？
Oh, yeah? And who do you like?
- 塞尔蒂克队   - 塞尔蒂克队？
- Celtics.     - Celtics? Ha!
他们连船都… 等等…
They couldn't hit a boat if... Wait.
他们很烂 好吗？
They suck, all right?
闭嘴 人家有在重建…
Shut up. You know, it's a rebuilding year. You...
- 啊哈   - 噢
- Aah! Aah!     - Oh. Aah.
我去叫爸爸 嘿
Uh, let me get the father. Hey!
宝宝的爸爸快点来
We need a father over here! We need a father!
没有爸爸
There's no father.
哦
Oh. Oh.
喔 抱歉
Oh, sorry.
没关系 我没事
Oh, that's okay. I'm fine. I'm...
- 哦   - 噢…
- Oh!     - Oh, uh...
好的 来这边
Okay. All right. Uh, right this way.
其他的孕妇好像都走进这里
All the other pregnant women seem to be going in here.
好
Okay.
他们小小胖胖的 让人爱不释手
They're tiny and chubby. And so sweet to touch
很快他们长大成人 对你憎恨不已
But soon they'll grow up And resent you so much
对你大呼大叫让你感到不解
Now they're yelling at you And you don't know why
惹你伤心落泪
And you cry and you cry and you cry
- 谢了 罗斯   - 我付钱是请你别唱了
- Thanks, Ross.     - Yeah. I'm paying you to stop.
好吧
Okay.
喔 快看 是双胞胎 喔 好可爱喔
Oh, look, twins. Hi, guys. Oh, cute, cute.
不公平 我一个都没有 为什么她有两个？
No fair. I don't even have one. How come they get two?
- 有一天你会有的   - 是吗？什么时候？
- You'll get one.     - Oh, yeah? When?
这么说好了
I'll tell you what.
如果我们俩到了40岁都还没结婚
When we're 40, if neither of us are married...
你说我们俩一起生一个好不好？
...what do you say you and I have one?
我为何到40岁还没结婚？
Why won't I be married when I'm 40?
喔 不… 我只是说假设
Oh, no, no, no. I just meant hypothetically.
好吧 那假设性的说 我为何到40还没嫁人？
Okay, hypothetically, why won't I be married when I'm 40?
- 不是 不是   - 为什么？
- No, no, no.     - No, no, what is it? Seriously.
我有什么原因嫁不出去吗？
Is there something fundamentally unmarriable about me?
- 呃…   - 说啊？
- Uh... Uh...     - Well?
老天 这降落伞根本是个背包
Dear God. This parachute is a knapsack.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey. Ooh.
- 喔 看看你穿这么美   - 嗯
- Look at you, dressy-dress.     - Yeah.
你回家换衣服？
Did you go home and change?
这是重要的日子 我想美美的
Yeah, well, it's an important day. I wanna look nice.
法兰兹布劳医生来了吗？
Um, has Dr. Franzblau been by?
我没见到他
No, I haven't seen him.
那他在哪？他应该在这的
Well, where is he? He is supposed to be here.
如果宝宝需要他怎么办？
What if the baby needs him?
瑞秋 你迷恋医生是怎么回事？
Rachel, what is the deal with you and doctors?
- 你父亲是医生吗？ - 是啊 为什么？
- Is, like, your father a doctor?     - Yeah. Why?
没什么
No reason.
妈妈 我们说过了
Mom, we've been through this.
不 我不要打给他
No, I am not calling him.
我不在乎他是孩子的爹 他是混蛋
I don't care if it is his kid. The guy's a jerk.
不 我不是一个人 乔伊在这
No, I am not alone. Joey's here.
什么叫 "哪个乔伊"？
What do you mean, "Joey who?"
哪个乔伊？
Joey who?
- 崔比亚尼   - 乔伊•崔比亚尼
- Tribbiani.     - Joey Tribbiani.
是的 好 等一下
Yes. Okay. Hold on.
- 她要跟你说话   - 不
- She wants to talk to you.     - No.
电话拿去
Take the phone.
喂 是 是我
Hi. Yeah, it's me.
不 我们只是朋友
Oh, no, no, no. We're just friends. Yeah.
是 我是单身
Yeah, I'm single.
25岁
Twenty-five.
演员
An actor.
喂？
Hello?
- 她不太懂电话礼仪   - 是啊
- She's not much of a phone person.     - Yeah.
所以 孩子的爸做了什么？
So, uh, what's the deal with this father guy?
如果有人怀了我的孩子 我会想要知道的
I mean, if someone was having my baby somewhere, I'd wanna know about it.
尼克队迷 我有兴趣知道你对为人父的想法吗？不
Hey, Knick fan, am I interested in your views on fatherhood? Um, no.
好吧 或许我该走了
Okay. Uh, look, maybe I should just go.
- 或许是   - 祝你好运
- Maybe you should.     - Good luck.
保重
And, uh, take care, huh?
你知道塞尔蒂克队的问题吗？他们让球员管理球队
Know what the Celtics' problem is? They let the players run the team.
才不是那样
Oh, that is so not true.
- 就是那样   - 不是
- Oh, it is. It is.     - It isn't. Isn't.
- 呼吸   - 呼吸
- Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.     - Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
我受不了了
You're gonna kill me!
- 再15秒 14 13 12…   - 数快一点
- Fifteen more seconds. Fourteen, 13, 12...     - Count faster.
没事的 这一切都是为了乔弟 想着他就好
It's gonna be okay. We're doing it for Jordy. Keep focusing on Jordy.
乔弟到底是谁？
Who the hell is Jordy?
- 你儿子   - 哇…
- Your son.     - Whoa, whoa whoa.
我儿子不叫乔弟
I don't have a son named Jordy.
我们说好要叫洁米的
We all agreed, my son's name is Jamie.
苏珊的第一任女友也叫洁米
Well, Jamie was the name of Susan's first girlfriend...
所以我们改回乔弟
...so we went back to Jordy.
哇…
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
你说什么改回乔弟？我们从没谈过乔弟这名字
What do you mean, "back to Jordy"? We never landed on Jordy.
在整个取名字的失败过程 我们压根没提过
We just passed by it during the whole Jesse/Cody/Dillon fiasco.
噢 噢…
Ow, ow, ow!
- 怎么了？ - 喔 小腿抽筋
- What? What? What?     - Leg cramp, leg cramp.
- 我来   - 我来 我在弄了
- I got it. I got it.     - I got it. I'm doing it.
你能跟她睡觉 小腿给我
You get to sleep with her. I get the cramps.
不 我来
No, you don't.
- 够了 你们都出去   - 什么？
- That is it. I want both of you out.     - What?
- 她开始的   - 是他
- She started it.     - He started it.
我不管
I don't care.
我努力想把一个人从身体生出来
I'm trying to get a person out of my body here...
你们这不是在帮我 现在出去
...and you're not making it any easier. Now go!
- 太感谢了   - 看你干的好事
- Thanks a lot.     - See what you did?
- 听我说…   - 出去
- Yeah. Listen...     - Out.
呼吸 呼吸 呼吸
Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
喔 不
Oh, no.
呃
Ew.
那是什么？有东西爆出来了
What is that? Something exploded.
她只是羊水破了 冷静点
It's just her water breaking. Calm down, will you?
羊水破了？什么意思？那是什么？
Water breaking? What do you mean? What's that, water breaking?
呼吸…
Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
- 拜托 都是你的错   - 为何是我的错？
- Oh, please. This is so your fault.     - How? How is this my fault?
在你出现以前 卡萝从没把我赶出门过
Look, Carol never threw me out of a room before you came along.
我还没出现之前 卡萝有很多事没做过
Well, there's a lot of things Carol never did before I came along.
- 你是在耍聪明？ - 你觉得我威胁到你…
- Are you trying to be clever?     - You are so threatened by me.
- 所有的事都不太对   - 嘿 好了 够了
- Everything I say is a problem.     - Hey, hey, hey. Okay. All right.
进去里面
That's it. Get in here. Come on.
天啊 你们两个 我真不敢相信
My God, you guys. I don't believe you.
这里有孩子等着出世
There are children coming into the world in this very building...
他们该听到的第一个声音 不是你们负面的争吵
...and your fighting noises are not the first thing they should be hearing.
所以你们别吵了 闭嘴
So just stop all the yelling! Just stop it!
对 苏珊
Yeah, Susan.
别逼我再这么做 我不喜欢拉高嗓音
Don't make me do this again! I don't like my voice like this!
谁想听听一件无奈的事？
Okay, who wants to hear something ironic?
快来人啊
Help!
- 拜托   - 快来人啊
- Come on!     - Help!
- 我的孩子要生了   - 哈罗
- I'm having a baby in there!     - Hello?
- 来人啊   - 好吧 大家拄后退
- Help!     - Okay, everyone stand back.
噢
Ow.
他…们…到…了没？
Are they here yet?
还没 你别担心 我们会找到他们的
No, honey, but don't worry, we're gonna find them.
在找到之前 我们都在这 好吗？
And until we do, we are all here for you, okay?
- 好   - 好喔
- Okay. Okay.     - Okay?
你刚说巴黎 那听起来很棒
Anyway, you were telling me about Paris. It sounds wonderful.
有一家很棒的点心店 就在我饭店旁边
It really was. There was this great little pastry shop right by my hotel...
很好 亲爱的
There you go, dear. You...
加油 莉蒂雅 你可以的
Come on, Lydia, you can do it. Push.
用力挤… 用力…
Push him out, push him out. Harder, harder.
用力挤… 出来
Push him out, push him out. Way out.
我们抢球的动作要快
Let's get that ball and really move. Hey, hey. Ho, ho.
我们…
Let's get...
我只是… 好吧
I was just... Yeah, okay.
用力…
Push, push, push.
你要干嘛？把门吸开？
What are you gonna do, suck the door open?
- 来人啊…   - 来人啊
- Help! Help! Help!     - Help!
他们在隔天找到他们的尸体
And they found their bodies The very next day
他们在隔天找到他们的…
And they found their bodies The very next...
啦啦…
La, la, la, la, la, la
来人啊
Help!
妈妈 一切都很顺利 罗斯很好 他…
No, Mom, everything's going fine, really. Yeah, Ross is great. He's, uh...
他在另外一个地方 不 他走了
He's in a whole other place. Yeah. No, he's gone.
不 你不需要飞回来 真的
No, no, you don't have to fly back. Really.
什么叫 "这可能是你唯一的机会"？
What do you mean, this might be your only chance?
别说了好吗？我才26岁
Oh. Would you stop? I'm only 26.
我都还没想到孩子的事
I'm not even thinking about babies yet.
- 你去哪了？ - 刚生了个孩子
- Where have you been?     - Oh, I just had a baby.
恭喜了
Mazel tov.
我不知道 有可能是1小时或3小时
I don't know. It could be an hour, it could be three.
但放轻松点 她很好
But relax, she's doing great.
所以 你最近有跟人交往吗？
So, uh, tell me, are you currently involved with anyone?
没有 现在没有 没有
No. No, not at... At the moment, no, I'm not, no.
- 你呢？ - 不
- Are you?     - No, no.
要找女人跟我约会很难
It's hard enough to get women to go out with me.
是啊 帅的医生都这样
Heh. Right, yeah, I've heard that about cute doctors.
不 是真的
No, no, really.
我猜是因为我花很多时间…
I suppose it's because I spend so much time, you know...
在我的工作上
...where I do.
- 哦   - 嗯
- Oh.     - Mm.
我试着不让工作影响我个人生活 但那很难
I try not to let work affect my personal life, but it's hard when you do...
做我这样的事就像…
...what I do. It's like, uh...
好吧 比如说 你做哪一行？
Well, for instance, what do you do?
- 我是服务生   - 好吧
- I'm a waitress.     - Okay, all right.
难道你没有 当你很晚回到家
Well, aren't there times when you come home at the end of the day...
会不想再见到任何一杯咖啡的经验？
...and you're just like, "If I see one more cup of coffee..."
对 我懂
Ahem. Yeah. Gotcha.
- 我去看看你的朋友   - 好的 没问题
- I'm gonna check up on your friend.     - Okay, that's fine.
- 你怎么知道我在这？ - 你妈妈打电话给我
- So how did you know I was even here?     - Your mom called me.
所以这就是她？
So is this her?
不 这是借来的
No, this is a loaner.
很抱歉我让你孤单分娩
Listen, I'm sorry you had to do this by yourself.
我不孤单 我有医生 护士 还有个善心男士
Oh. I wasn't by myself. I had a doctor, a nurse and a helper guy.
你知道谁赢了比赛吗？
So did you see who won the game?
尼克队赢了10分 他们很烂
Yeah, Knicks by 10. They suck.
他们也没那么烂啦
Eh, they're not so bad.
拜托…
Come on. Come on.
该死… 都是你的错
Damn it, damn it, damn it. This is all your fault.
这应该是我生命中最美好的一天
This is supposed to be, like, the greatest day of my life.
我儿子要出生了 我应该在场的
My son is being born, and I should be in there, you know?
而不是跟你困在柜子里
Instead I'm stuck in a closet with you.
我爱的女人要生了 我跟你一样期待这一天
I've been waiting for this just as much as you have.
相信我 没有人像我这么期待这天的
Believe me, no one has been waiting for this as much as I have, okay?
你知道好笑的是什么吗？
And you know what the funny thing is?
生完后 孩子可以跟你回去
When this day is over, you get to go home with the baby.
- 而我剩什么？ - 你是孩子的父亲
- Where does that leave me?     - You get to be the father.
大家都知道你是谁 我算什么？有父亲节 母亲节
Everyone knows who you are. Who am I? There's Father's Day. There's Mother's Day.
没有女同志情人节
There's no Lesbian Lover Day.
每天都是女同志情人节
Every day is Lesbian Lover Day.
这真是太棒了
This is so great.
解释一下好吗？
You wanna explain that?
我是说 我小时候 父亲就丢下我
I mean, well, because when I was growing up, you know, my dad left...
我母亲死了 而我继父去坐牢
...and my mother died, and my stepfather went to jail.
我几乎没有任何父母亲的疼爱
So I barely had enough pieces of parents to make one whole one.
而这个宝宝有三个父母
And here's this little baby who has like three whole parents...
他们是如此关心他 还为此争吵谁最爱他
...who care about it so much that they fight over who gets to love it the most...
宝宝甚至还没出生呢
...and it's not even born yet.
他是世上最幸运的宝宝
It's just the luckiest baby in the whole world.
对不起 你们在吵架
I'm sorry. You were fighting.
他们在哪？
Where are they?
- 他们很快就会来的   - 他们不会错过这一刻的
- I'm sure they'll be here soon.     - They wouldn't miss this.
放轻松 你只开了9公分 宝宝还不会出来
Relax. You're only at nine centimeters, and the baby's at zero station.
你真令我感到害怕
Okay, you are really frightening me.
救救我好吗？有人要挖出我的心脏
Somebody wanna help me? Trying to rip out my heart.
太好了 有人看到奶头吗？
Uh... Oh, that's great. Anybody seen a nipple?
10公分了 开始了
All right. Ten centimeters. Here we go.
- 甜心 要开始用力了   - 但他们还没到
- All right, honey, time to start pushing.     - But they're not here yet.
抱歉 宝宝不能等的
Sorry, I can't tell the baby to wait for them.
喔 天啊
Oh, God.
好了 通气孔打开了
Okay, got the vent open.
嗨 我是班
Hi, I'm Ben.
我是医院工作员班
I'm hospital worker Ben.
班要去救援了
It's Ben to the rescue.
- 啦…   - 好…
- La, la, la     - Okay, okay, okay.
- 班 你好了没？ - 好了
- Ben, you ready?     - Yeah.
- 脚踩上来   - 好
- All right, give me your foot.     - Okay.
- 数到3 班 1 2 3   - 噢
- Okay, on three, Ben. One, two, three. Unh.     - Ooh.
- 加油 班 就是这样 班   - 好了
- Come on, Ben. Okay. That's it, Ben.     - Okay. Uh-huh.
你看到什么？
What do you see?
苏珊 看来像是黑黑的通气孔
Well, Susan, I see what appears to be a dark vent.
等等
Wait.
是的 没错 是黑黑的通气孔
Yes, it is, in fact, a dark vent.
菲比 门开了…
Pheebs, it's open! It's open!
等等 你们的脚还在这
Wait! You forgot your legs!
- 用力…   - 我们来了…
- Push. Push.     - We're here!
- 我们来了   - 你们死哪儿去了？
- We're here.     - Where have you been?!
这故事很长
Long story, honey.
我要你继续用力
All right, Carol, I need you to keep pushing.
我需要… 对不起 我要拿这个
I need... Excuse me, can I have this?
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
好…
All right, all right.
太多人在这了 而且又有一个要出来
There's too many people in this room. There's about to be one more.
如果不是前夫或女同志伴侣的人 请出去
So anybody who's not an ex-husband or a lesbian life partner, out you go.
- 快点 出去   - 祝你好运
- Come on, out.       - Okay, good luck.
- 再见   - 祝你们幸运
- Bye, bye, bye.     - Good luck, you guys, good luck.
请问一下 一定要是卡萝的女同志伴侣才行吗？
Let me ask you, do you have to be Carol's lesbian life partner?
出去
Out.
好了 他要出来了
All right. All right, he's crowning. Here he comes.
让我看 我一定要看
Let me see. I gotta see, I gotta see.
哦…
Oh... Oh.
一颗头
Oh! A head.
那好大 卡萝 你如何办到的？
Oh. It's huge. Carol, how are you doing this?
你这不是在帮我
Not helping.
你做得很好
You're doing great. You're doing fine.
- 嘿？ - 喔 对不起
- Hello?     - Oh, sorry.
你看到什么…？
What do you see? What do you see?
头 肩膀和手臂出来了
We got a head, we got shoulders, we got arms, we got...
喔 看那小小的手指
Oh, look at the little... The fingers.
胸部和肚子…
Oh, a chest and a stomach...
是个男孩 货真价实
...and it's a boy, definitely a boy.
腿 膝盖和脚
All right. Okay, legs, knees and feet.
哦…
Oh, oh.
他出来了
He's here. He's...
他是一个人
He's a person.
噢…
Oh!
- 看啊   - 他看起来像谁？
- Look at that.     - What does he look like?
有点像我的叔叔艾德裹着果冻
Kind of like my Uncle Ed, covered in Jell-O.
真的？
Really?
哈罗 他很漂亮
You guys, he's beautiful.
谢了 菲比
Aw, thanks, Pheebs.
别大声叫 但我们还没替宝宝取名字
No shouting, but we still need a name for this little guy.
小班怎么样？
How about Ben?
我喜欢小班
I like Ben.
小班
Ben.
- 小班很好   - 是吗？
- Ha, ha. Ben's good.     - Yeah?
你之前怎么都没提到？
How come you never mentioned Ben before?
- 我们刚刚才想出来的   - 哈
- We, uh, just cooked it up.     - Ha, ha.
那就是我们不在这里时 正在做的事
That's what we were off doing.
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey.
- 我们可以进来吗？ - 进来…
- Can we come in?     - Yeah, come in. Come in.
我知道…
I know. I know.
各位 我要你们见见一个人
Everybody, there's someone I'd like you to meet.
对 这位是小班
Yeah. This is Ben.
- 嗨 小班   - 嗨 小班
- Hi, Ben.     - Hi, Ben.
- 小班 这是大伙儿   - 嗨 小班
- Ben, this is everybody.     - Hey, Ben.
苏珊 他看起来就像你
Susan, he looks just like you.
谢谢
Thanks. Ha, ha.
天啊 我真不敢相信 我们当中有人生了宝宝
Oh, God, I can't believe one of us actually has one of these.
我知道 我还是宝宝
I know. I still am one of these.
- 罗斯？ - 怎样？
- Ross? Yeah?
我可以吗？
Can I?
好的 小心头 你要…
Okay, the head, the head. You gotta...
嗨 小班 嗨
Hi, Ben. Hi.
我是摩妮卡姑姑 你的姑姑
I'm your Aunt Monica. Yes, I am.
摩妮卡姑姑
I'm your Aunt Monica.
我…
I...
我会随时都带口香糖的
I will always have gum.
小班
Ben...
我要你知道有时候我可能
...I want you to know that there may be some times...
不会在你身边
...when I may not be around...
像这样
...like this.
但我总是会回来的
But I'll still always come back...
像这样
...like this.
而有时候 我可能会离开久一点
And sometimes I may be away longer...
像这样
...like this.
但我总是会回到你身边的
But I'll still always come back...
就像这样
...like this.
有时候 我会要你去盗垒 那时我会这样做
And sometimes I'll want you to steal third, and I'll go like this.
他好奇妙
Oh, he is so amazing.
我知道 看看他
Yeah, I know. Look at him.
小班…
Ben.
嘿 小班
Hey, Ben.
没反应 我不认为他叫小班
Nothing. I don't think that's his name.
他要闭上眼睛了 看
Oh, look, look, he's closing his eyes.
他张开眼睛了 看
Oh, look, he's opening his eyes.
他的动作不多 对吧？
He doesn't do much, does he?
没错 就是这样了
Nope, this is pretty much it.
- 你们要喝咖啡吗？ - 好
- You guys wanna get some coffee?     - Yeah.
待会儿再见
All right, I'll see you guys later.
嗨 班
Hi, Ben.
- 我爱你   - 嗨 小班
- I love you.     - Hi, Ben.
你看 他又要闭上眼睛了
Oh, look, he's closing his eyes again.